gmpartsdirect.com 2019-03-19

# GMPartsDirect.com | Privacy Policy

### Your privacy is our priority

Your security is important to us.  By using our site you are hereby agreeing to provide session information that is used for logistical and performance tracking. All session information is stored securely and anonymized. We anonymize any personally identifiable information (PII).

We will never share your information or email addresses with vendors, business partners or other organizations.

If you wish to have data information removed or to be "forgotten", [please contact us at: customerservice@gmpartsdirect.com](mailto:customerservice@gmpartsdirect.com) .

### What Information is Collected?

The information we learn from visitors helps us to personalize and continually improve our site. Basically, you can visit our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself but we do collect statistics on the amount of traffic and traffic patterns on this site.

Our Site's Staff does obtain and retain certain information as you email us directly and whenever you respond to website questions. We may analyze this data for marketing and technical purposes.

### Links to Third Party Sites

Our site may include links to other websites that are not under our control. You should review those policies before visiting those websites.

### Policy Changes

This policy is subject to change. If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on this privacy policy page.

If you have any questions [please contact us at: customerservice@gmpartsdirect.com](mailto:customerservice@gmpartsdirect.com) .

.
